<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><title type="text">One Among Us</title><subtitle type="html">One Among Us is a Chinese-Canadian not-for-profit corporation for transgender rights.</subtitle><updated>2023-04-11T10:08:43+00:00</updated><id>https://oneamongus.ca/</id><link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://oneamongus.ca/"/><link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://oneamongus.ca/atom.xml"/><author><name>One Among Us Transgender Support</name><uri>https://oneamongus.ca/</uri><email>info@one-among.us</email></author><rights>[CC BY 4.0](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/deed.en)</rights><generator uri="https://gohugo.io/" version="0.111.3">Hugo</generator><entry><title type="text">One Among Us Promotes Mental Health Among Members</title><link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://oneamongus.ca/posts/mh_promotion/"/><id>https://oneamongus.ca/posts/mh_promotion/</id><updated>2023-04-11T10:08:40+00:00</updated><published>2023-04-11T05:00:00-04:00</published><author><name>One Among Us Transgender Support</name><uri>https://oneamongus.ca/</uri><email>info@one-among.us</email></author><rights>[CC BY 4.0](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/deed.en)</rights><summary type="html">At One Among Us, we are committed to promoting mental health among our members, especially amidst the challenges posed by remote work, while also addressing the critical issues of self-cutting and overdose prevention.</summary><content type="html">&lt;p>At One Among Us, we are committed to promoting mental health among our members, especially amidst the challenges posed by remote work, while also addressing the critical issues of self-cutting and overdose prevention.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We recognize that substance abuse and self-injury are often rooted in social, economic, and environmental factors that can contribute to feelings of hopelessness, despair, and disconnection. To address these underlying causes, we have been working with mental health professionals to provide our members with the tools and support they need to overcome addiction and manage emotional distress.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Additionally, we are dedicated to raising awareness about these issues in our community and promoting a culture of empathy, compassion, and understanding. By fostering a supportive and inclusive environment, we hope to reduce the stigma and shame associated with substance abuse and self-injury and encourage individuals to seek the help they need.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As most of us are working from home and some overseas, we understand that the challenges posed by remote work can exacerbate mental health issues and contribute to feelings of isolation and disconnection. To address these challenges, we have been providing virtual resources and support to our members, including mental health hotlines, online support groups, and mental health webinars.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We believe that promoting mental health and preventing overdose and self-harm are essential to creating a healthier and more resilient community. By addressing the complex social causes of these issues and providing support and resources to our members, we hope to make a positive impact on the well-being of our members and the diversed trans, gender non-conforming, and queer community as a whole.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="../mh.png" alt="A parody of Chinese propaganda arts but showing the aim of preventing overdose and self-cutting" title="A parody of Chinese propaganda arts but showing our topic of preventing overdose and self-cutting.">&lt;/p></content></entry></feed>